

## **CONTACT ME**

- Ahmedabad, Gujarat
- **(** +91-7984026587
- shubhampatel12499
- in shubhampatel12499
- shubhampatel12499.github.io

## **EDUCATION**

### **Full Stack Web Developement**

Masai School, Bangalore April 2022 - March 2023

### **Bachelor in Mechanical Engineering**

Gujarat Technological University Aug 2016 - Sep 2020

### **Higher Secondary Education**

P.P.G Experimental High School Gujarat Education Board Mar 2015 - Mar 2016

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

React JS | Angular JS | Node JS | React Native | Flutter | Wordpress | Express | Mongo DB | Redux | Bootstrap | Material UI | Tailwind | Chakra UI | Mat | HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Typescript | DSA

### SOFT SKILLS

Leadership | Team Work | Problem Solving | Collaboration | Creativity

## **CERTIFICATE**

Angular - The Complete Guide

# SHUBHAM PATEL

Full-Stack Web Developer

### **PROFILE**

Intuitive and fast-learning developer with 2 years of experience in building web applications using JavaScript, CSS, React, Angular, and both MERN and MEAN stacks. Passionate about solving real-world problems through clean and efficient code. Looking to contribute as a full-stack developer in a growth-oriented tech environment.

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

**Jyoti Technosoft LLP** 

Jan 2024 - Present

Full - Stack Web Developer

**Facion Labs Private Limited** 

Jun 2023 - Jan 2024

Frontend Web Developer

Indian Space Research Organization (ISRO) Jan 2021 - Jan 2022

Mechanical Design Engineer (ISRO - SAC)

### **PROJECTS**

### **HRMS & Task Management System**

An integrated platform for managing employee attendance, leave, tasks, and performance.

Features: - User Registration & Login, Punch-In/Punch-Out, Leave Management, Performance Monitoring, Notifications, Reports, Admin Controls, etc.

Tech Stack:- React JS, Node JS, Express, Mongo DB, Redux, Material UI, D3 **Responsibilities**: - Developments, Debugging, Testing, Bug Fixes and R & D. Collaborative Project developed by a team of skilled professionals.

lo Sense.io 🏻 🍪



It is a Platform focused on addressing diverse company requirements.

Features: Overview Entity, Login & Register Page, Device Entity, Contacts Page, Notifications Entity, Triggers Entity, Dashboards, etc.

Tech Stack:- Angular JS, Bootstrap, Mat Library, Rxjs operators, High Charts **Responsibilities**: - Developments, Debugging, R & D, Version Upgrade, Bug Fixes. Collaborative Project developed by a team of Exceptional Developers.

### Shop Kart 🚺 🧇



It is a responsive E-commerce Website inspired by Flipkart.

Features: - Landing Page, Login & Signup Page, Product Page, Cart Page, Checkout Page, Create Backend and connect with Front-end.

**Tech Stack**:- React JS, Redux, Chakra UI, Node JS, Express, MongoDB Atlas Responsibility: - Navbar & Footer, Authentication, UI Responsiveness & Backend Collaborative Project developed by a team of five members in 5 days.

### **INTERESTS**

- Poetry Recitation & Writing
- Books

E-sports

To know and Read more about our Culture